<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<mod>
    <name>Thirallan: Alchemist Edition</name>
    <description>This is a mash up mod, it mashes the following mods into a whole new experience: Thirallan, Deathbourne, The Realm of Dragons, Robot Rebellion, and a whole new project!</description>
    <steamDesc>
      This mod is a kind of collection of my other mods, except they have all been redone to be much better mods. All into one star system. Are you ready to experience what these mods should've been like from the start?

      There are a few things to note currently:

      1. Speak to CaptAln after meeting him, or speak to Alchemist after making the Dragon Ship to unlock the system.

      2. The mods that will eventually be redone in this mod are as follows:

      Thirallan, The Realm of Dragons, Deathbourne, Robot Rebellion, and a completely new project.

      3. This mod is currently incomplete, the following things are either nonexistent or inaccessible at this current time:

      Realm of Dragons, Some of Thirallan, Deathbourne, and the new project.

      4. There is a placeholder sprite: the Farmer Scene Sprite is a placeholder for the character: Pyrrhos.

      5. This mod has been created for the KOZ Modding Competition.

      Have a bug, issue, or suggestion for the mod? You can come to say hi on Discord! Come to the Fancy Fish Games Discord Server or even better the Unofficial Aground Modding Team's Discord server

      OR if you don't use Discord but use GitHub, then consider making an issue on the Mod Github Page: https://github.com/jgrable634/Thirallan-Alchemist-Edition/issues

      Special Thanks to
      Airom for helping develop the Corruption Mechanic
      Etrotta for helping develop the Purifier Boss fight!
      AWG4 and ThaumTaf for the incredible artwork that's currently added and for the future
      https://nosoapradio.us (website) for developing the incredible music showcased in the mod (although the music was not created for the mod, it is under a creative commons attribution license.)
    </steamDesc>
    <tag>KOZModdingColosseum</tag>
    <author>Alchemist</author>
    <version>1.1.1</version>
    <requires>Full Version</requires>
    <loadAfter>Thirallan</loadAfter>
    <loadAfter>Deathbourne</loadAfter>
    <loadAfter>The Realm Of Dragons</loadAfter>
    <loadAfter>Spirits Plus</loadAfter>
    <loadAfter>Robot Rebellion</loadAfter>
    <init>
      <action>
        function _Thirallan_Format(id){ // Credit to Etrotta
          // return id;
          var final = "";
          var result; //defines with a null value
          var name = getText("world>"+id); //searchs for the vanilla name
          if (name != null) {
            result = name.getValue(); //if there is a name for it, use it
          }
          final += " " + result ; //adds the a space + the word to the phrase
          return final.substring(1); //removes the first thing bc it is just a space, like literally " "
        }
      </action>
      <include id="thirallan/mod.xml" child="init" />
      <include id="the_corruption/mod.xml" child="init" />
      <!-- <include id="deathbourne/mod.xml" child="init" /> -->
      <include id="realm_of_dragons/mod.xml" child="init" />
      <include id="robot_rebellion/mod.xml" child="init" />
      <include id="en_US.xml" includeRoot="true" />
      <include id="entry.xml" />
      <include id="arena/arena.xml" />

      <section if="getMod('thirallan') != null && getMod('thirallan').isEnabled()">
        <system id="thirallan" x="-50" />
      </section>

      <system id="alchemist_system" bgm="voyage" x="80" y="80" available="player.hasQuest('alchemist_system_alch') || player.hasQuest('alchemist_system_pres')">
        <planet id="thirallan_alchemist" tile="planet7" animation="planet.thirallan" orbit="orbit4" offsetX="53" offsetY="38" name="system.thirallan">
          <onJump><action>trace("jump to thirallan")</action></onJump>
        </planet>
        <planet id="ROD_planet" tile="ROD_planet" offsetX="50" offsetY="100" />
        <planet id="robot_rebellion" tile="planet2" animation="planet.start.dwarf" orbit="orbit1" offsetX="-75" offsetY="-4" name="planet.robot" />
        <planet id="corruption" tile="planet6" animation="planet.corruption" orbit="orbit3" offsetX="26" offsetY="-20" />
      </system>
    </init>
</mod>
